SHAHAB HESARAKI

Full-Stack Web Developer

Montreal, Quebec (willing to relocate) +1 (438) 883-9936 Shahabhes@gmail.com Linkedin.com/in/shahab-hesaraki

Motivated full-stack web developer with over three years of learning experience. Expertise in developing, debugging and providing the team with a wide range of suggestions. Fluent in English and Beginner in French.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express.js React.js, Node.js), HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, PHP, Laravel, AWS, Restful APIs, Git, GitHub, MySQL.

EDUCATION

•	Full-Stack Web Development Diploma (JS - React - Node), Concordia University	2022
•	Professional HTML-CSS Course, McGill University	2021
•	Back-end Development Diploma (PHP-Laravel), Tehran Institute of Technology	2020
	Front-end Development Diploma (HTML - CSS - JS), Tehran Institute of Technology	2020
	Bachelor in Management, Technical and Vocational University of Tehran	2014-2018

EXPERIENCE

Sales Agent, IO Solutions Contact Center Inc. (Canada)

2021-Present

- Establish a climate of trust with the client and analyze them in order to promote products and services.
- Interact with customers by phone, advise and offer solutions adapted to their needs.

Web Developer (Internship), MehrYasan, Tehran (Iran)

2020-2021

- Writing back-end code and building efficient PHP modules.
- Developing PHP back-end with an optimized MySQL database.

IT Technician, ZibaNovin Print, Tehran (Iran)

2015-2019

- Troubleshooting hardware and software issues and supporting network users.
- Installation and upgrading anti-virus software and security systems.

RELEVANT PROJECTS (Portfolio: https://shahab-hesaraki-portfolio.netlify.app)

News Project (https://github.com/shahabhesaraki-dev/Concordia-FinalProject)

A fully functional news website that admin can send a new post, delete and edit the posts and users can search for news, leave comments, view related posts, popular posts, and last news. **Technology used:** HTML, CSS, React, Node., Express.is, MongoDB

E-Commerce Project (https://github.com/shahabhesaraki-dev/E-Commerce-Project)

A watch store that is completely functional. It is possible to add your items to the cart and purchase them and get the confirmation number. Capable of searching for watches, viewing popular models, and selecting sales products. <u>Technology used:</u> HTML, CSS, React, Node,, Express.js, MongoDB

Flight Ticket Project (https://github.com/shahabhesaraki-dev/SlingAir)

A ticket booking application that allows you to reserve a ticket as well as update and delete it. **Technology used:** HTML, CSS, React, Node., Express.is, MongoDB

Animal Care Project (https://github.com/shahabhesaraki-dev/animalCare)

A Twitter-like application for finding a pet nurse while you are unavailable to care your pet for a few days. <u>Technology used:</u> HTML, CSS, React, Node, Express.js